[Description] The presenter appears on screen in front of the game Hogwarts Legacy. He starts speaking in an animated tone.
[Descripción] El presentador aparece en pantalla frente al videojuego Hogwarts Legacy. Comienza a hablar con tono animado.
[Description] In the game, the character casts the Revelio spell. Bright objects with question mark symbols appear.
[Descripción] En el juego, el personaje lanza el hechizo Revelio. Aparecen objetos brillantes con símbolos de interrogación.
[Description] The character moves through different rooms in search of the objects.
[Descripción] El personaje se mueve por diferentes habitaciones en busca de los objetos.
[Description] The character approaches a mysterious door and presses a button to display a sequence of numbers and symbols.
[Descripción] Se acerca a una puerta misteriosa y pulsa un botón para mostrar una secuencia de números y símbolos.
[Description] The numbers 5 and 12 appear on the door's mechanism.
[Descripción] Aparecen los números 5 y 12 en el mecanismo de la puerta.
[Description] The presenter zooms in on the door to explain the number puzzle.
[Descripción] El presentador hace zoom en la puerta para explicar el acertijo numérico.
[Description] A triangle with numbers and symbols at its vertices appears on the screen.
[Descripción] En la pantalla se muestra un triángulo con números y símbolos en los vértices.
[Description] A guide is shown with the game's symbols and their corresponding numerical values from 0 to 9.
[Descripción] Se muestra una guía con los símbolos del juego y su valor numérico correspondiente del 0 al 9.
[Description] The presenter points to the symbols and explains how values are assigned to each.
[Descripción] El presentador señala los símbolos y explica cómo se asignan valores a cada uno.
[Description] The first puzzle is solved by adding the values: 3 + 0 + 2.
[Descripción] Se resuelve el primer acertijo sumando los valores: 3 + 0 + 2.
[Description] A symbol in the shape of a goat is selected as the answer.
[Descripción] Se selecciona un símbolo en forma de cabra como respuesta.
[Description] The cursor highlights the symbols in order: 0, 1, 2.
[Descripción] El cursor señala los símbolos en orden: 0, 1, 2.
[Description] It is confirmed that the sum matches the target number.
[Descripción] Se confirma que la suma coincide con el número objetivo.
[Description] The character spins the object with a question mark and selects the correct symbol.
[Descripción] El personaje gira el objeto con un interrogante y selecciona el símbolo correcto.
[Description] The second puzzle is tackled, which results in the number 12.
[Descripción] Se pasa al segundo acertijo que tiene como resultado el número 12.
[Description] The cursor moves to the symbol already visible on the screen.
[Descripción] El cursor se mueve hacia el símbolo ya visible en pantalla.
[Description] The symbol shown is the unicorn, identified as value 1.
[Descripción] El símbolo mostrado es el unicornio, identificado como valor 1.
[Description] The presenter continues explaining the logic behind the puzzle.
[Descripción] El presentador continúa explicando la lógica del acertijo.
[Description] The values 1 + 4 + 7 are added, and the symbol in the shape of an octopus is selected.
[Descripción] Se suman los valores 1 + 4 + 7, y se selecciona el símbolo con forma de pulpo.
[Description] The character interacts with the second spinning object and picks the correct symbol.
[Descripción] El personaje interactúa con el segundo objeto giratorio y elige el símbolo correcto.
[Description] The character stands in front of the door and presses the button to open it.
[Descripción] El personaje se coloca frente a la puerta y pulsa el botón para abrirla.
[Description] The door slowly opens, revealing a secret room with a glowing chest inside.
[Descripción] La puerta se abre lentamente y revela una sala secreta con un cofre brillante en su interior.